hi you must be Liam hey buddy how are
you feeling today I'm feeling fine
doctor
this is million glass she's from the
Make A Wish Foundation
Marion how are you feeling today Liam
I'm fine Marion glass okay well I have
some news that might make you feel a
little better huh we have to make a wish
foundation make dreams come true for
little boys and little girls who are
very sick
just like you there are no children like
me Marion Oh course not you're one of a
kind but we're gonna make any dream come
true that you could ever have okay
anything that's right buddy
that's right would would you like to
play with your favorite basketball team
Oh what about being Superman for a day I
wish to drown
what - drowning me in the bathtub no
holding breath escapes his body water
all the while singing
[Music]
Liam should surely we don't want to hurt
other people now do we kiddo any
anything else flying or hot-air balloon
or meet a celebrity my new wish is to
lean over the body of a dying man and
put my lips on his stealing his last
breath Liam no absolutely not I don't
even know where you're I wish to take
all the prosthetic legs in the hospital
when massive creature hey Liam I am so
sorry mr. Claus
it's all right he he doesn't know what
he's saying I wish to pee in your mouth
what both of you mine
especially you oh I wish to pee in both
of your mouths as I stand over you I'll
need a glass of water and enough little
6 dr. Gupta no you are reprehensible you
are evil you are a devil child dr. Gupta
he's not a devil child he's just a child
you have no business working in a
pediatric ward what I'm gonna report you
[Music]
ah shame on you Gupta you really have
said Mary my thing you've made me
question everything that I've ever
believed about the essential goodness of
[Music]
[Applause]